{
    "subject": "resource/The_Sounds",
    "predicate": "ontology/activeYearsStartYear",
    "object": "1999",
    "human_readable": "The Sounds started their active years in 1999.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8412519693374634,
            "question": "When did The Sounds begin their active years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7757034301757812,
            "question": "Has The Sounds released any albums since their start in 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3891370892524719,
            "question": "In what decade did The Sounds emerge as a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37696897983551025,
            "question": "Is The Sounds a relatively new or established band based on their starting year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34986376762390137,
            "question": "What might be some key influences on The Sounds' music based on their starting year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2918604016304016,
            "question": "Where did The Sounds originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20579153299331665,
            "question": "What year marked the start of The Sounds' musical journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09956628829240799,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations or awards associated with The Sounds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0706079751253128,
            "question": "What musical genre is The Sounds most associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05049135163426399,
            "question": "Can you name any popular songs by The Sounds?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Sounds started their active years in 1999.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4510_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical genre is The Sounds most associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4510_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable collaborations or awards associated with The Sounds?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4510_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year marked the start of The Sounds' musical journey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4510_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4510_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the band \"The Sounds\" starting their active years in 1999. The document related to Prince's album '1999' discusses activities in 1982 and 1999, but it does not mention \"The Sounds.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The text explicitly states that Prince recorded his album \"1999\" in 1982, which is 17 years before the year 1999. Therefore, there's no indication that The Sounds started their active years in 1999.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context discusses Prince's album \"1999\" which was released in 1982,  and the article states that it was recorded while a future year was still seventeen years away.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the Sound Of list was first conducted by BBC News in 2003.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions \"1999\" as a significant album by Prince, not as the start of The Sounds' active years. Moreover, there is no mention or implication of The Sounds starting their active years in 1999.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}